Guide to the University of California, Santa Barbara Office of Public Events Collection
Department of Special Collections
University of California, Santa Barbara Office of Public Events Collection
1950-2006
UArch 84
University of California, Santa Barbara. Office of Public Events
0.2 linear feet (1 half-sized document box)
University of California, Santa Barbara. Library. Dept. of Special Collections Santa Barbara, CA 93106
The collection contains memos, and event flyers and invitations. Events include Charter Day, Parents' and Family Weekend, and Commencement.
Access Restrictions
None.
Acquisition Information
Undetermined.
Scope and Content of Collection
"The Office of Public Events plans and orchestrates many major campus events, including Parents' and Family Weekend and all of UCSB's commencement ceremonies. In addition, the office frequently assists individual campus departments in arranging special events and receptions."
From Office of Public Events page, http://www.instadv.ucsb.edu/pe/index.shtml
The office organizes Commencement and Parents' and Family Weekend, among other events. The Office of Public Events was previously known as the Office of Public Ceremonies / Committee on Public Ceremonies, then briefly the Office of Public Events Ceremonies.
The collection is arranged chronologically and contains memos, and event flyers and invitations. Events include Charter Day, Parents' and Family Weekend, and Commencement.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
University of California, Santa Barbara. Office of Public Events
Related Material
Commencement Program, annual publication in University Archives Serials.
Office of Public Information subject files, UArch 12 Many files on Commencement and Charter Day, as well as file on Parents' Weekend.
Office of the Chancellor, Chancellors' records, UArch 17 Contains files on Chancellor Cheadle's Commencement and Charter Day speeches.
Academic Senate records, UArch 13 File on Charter Day.
Office of Public Events website: http://www.instadv.ucsb.edu/pe/index.shtml
- Office of Public Ceremonies
  - Memos, 1950-1979 (Box-folder 1: 1)
  - Invitations, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 1: 2)
  - Flyers, 1967-1976 (Box-folder 1: 3)
  - Commencement, 1971-1979 (Box-folder 1: 4)
- Office of Public Events Ceremonies
  - Memos, 1981 (Box-folder 1: 5)
  - Flyers, 1980 (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Commencement, 1980 (Box-folder 1: 7)
- Office of Public Events
  - Memos, 1989-2000 (Box-folder 1: 8)
  - Flyers, 1990-2006 (Box-folder 1: 9)
  - Commencement, 1997 (Box-folder 1: 10)